Guide to the Stanford University Poster Collection SC1030
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University poster collection
circa 1890s-2015
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University
Reeds, Karen Meier.
SC1030
1625 item(s)
Information about Access
Open for research.
Other Finding Aids
A searchable database of posters in this collection is also available.
Scope and Contents
Poster collection documenting academic and student life at Stanford University, including athletics, drama, lectures, films, musical events, organizations, dances, parties and other social events, and political activities. Of note are 23 original posters by Karen Meier Reeds for events on campus, 1964 to 1968.
College students -- California; Stanford University -- History.; Posters.; Stanford University; Reeds, Karen Meier.
- Posters
  - 11th Annual Stanford Pow Wow, 1982; 530-35; 16.5 x 22 inches (Box C7)
    Miscellaneous, Student
  - 1996-97 Chicana/o Colloquia: History / Memory / Recognition, 212-5; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
    Chicana/o Fellows Program
  - 1999-2000 Stanford [calendar]. Includes important campus phone numbers and other information, 2002-003; 38 x 25 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
    Administration
  - 2012 Women's Volleyball: The Cardinal Rules!, 2015-033; 18 x 24 inches (Box C11)
  - 24th Annual Stanford Powwow Celebrating Our Youth: The Future of Native America May 12-14, 1995, 2002-016 (Box D1)
  - 25 May the Mendicants are coming out with a new stereo LP "A Fello Needs a Girl" [1966], 524-54; 22 x 14 inches (Box C5)
    Music, Student
  - 26th Annual Stanford Powwow May 9, 10, 11 1997 Honoring Our Warriors, 2002-014; 16 x 20 inches (Box C3)
  - 3 Plays by Stanford Writers, 1947; 513-25; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
    Student Drama Productions Misc.
  - 38th Annual Stanford Powwow, May 8-10, 2009; 2009-008; 22 x 17 inches (Box D1)
  - 5 de Mayo reflexiones sobre nuestra lucha. Stanford University Apriil 26-May 5 [1979]. [list of activies for week; Cesar Chavez was speaker on May 3], 2005-005; 22.5 x 14.25 inches (Box C4)
  - 500 Thanks, Monty!!! Stanford Basketball Home of Champions, 2003-; 2003-003; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
    General note
    Celebrating Coach Montgomery's 500th win; handed out at game.
    Athletics
  - 50th Anniversary Festival and Promenade, 1941; 7; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
    Directional
  - 8 color films from the first-year students in the MFA Program in Documentary Film and Video. Friday, June 11 7:30pm Annenberg Auditorium, 2010-; 2010-012; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - A Bill of One-Act Plays, Un-dated; 502-1; 7 x 11 inches (Box A4)
    Stanford Dramatic Production Classes
  - A Bill of One-Act Plays, Un-dated; 502-3; 7 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - A Bill of One-Act Plays, Un-dated; 502-6; 7 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - A California Souvenir, Un-dated; 905-28; 11 x 15 inches (Box not specified)
    Miscellaneous
  - A Century of Revolutions Lenin to Gorbachev. An Exhibit ot Papers and Documents..., 1990; 215-02; 14x20 1/2 inches (Box B1)
    Hoover Institution-Exhibits
  - A Comic Lecture by Mr. Edwin Stevens, Un-dated; 399; 13 x 21 inches (Box map case)
    Non-Stanford Speakers-Lectures
  - A Day on the Farm. Stanford Red Barn Festival 11th Annual. Saturday August 19, 2000, 2003-025; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - "A Doll's House", 1947; 513-26; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - A Festival of Poets, 1969; 371; 11 x 15 inches (Box A2)
  - "A Funny Thing Happened on the way to the Forum", 1968; 510-3; 11 x 17 inches (Box C6)
    MAFIA Productions
  - "A Highland Fling", October 25-27, 1945; 511-2; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
    Stanford Players Productions
  - "A Kiss for Cinderella", Un-dated; 507-8; 14 x 20 in (Box C6)
    English Club Productions
  - A Modern Challenge to College Men, Un-dated; 406; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Ansel Adams and Wallace Stegner: A Conversation, 1982 Oct 24; 2011-008; 14x22 inches (Box B2)
  - A poetry reading with Andri Voznesensky with an introduction by Lawrence Ferlinghetti, Stanford Humanities Center, April 29, 2004, 2005-002; 11x17 inches (Box B2)
  - A Residency in Tribute to Katherine Dunham; Choreographer, Anthropologist, Educator, 1989 May 1-27; 2015-030; 18 x 22 inches (Box C11)
  - A symposium ... in honor of Professor Elliot Eisner's retirement from teaching. Saturday October 7, 2006-., 2008-008; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - A Talk by the Consul-General of Brazil, 1955; 318; 14x22 inches (Box C1)
  - A Third Address to Stanford Men by Mr. Mott: "Shall the Student Disbileve or Overcome?", 1901-; 307; 14 x 23 inches (Box C1)
  - "A Trick for a Trophy", Un-dated; 513-37; 42 x 28 inches (Box C7)
  - "A Visit to Stanford University", Un-dated; 905-12; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - A Young Man is Dead..and American troups are occupying an Aemrican city--CAN BERKELEY HAPPEN HERE?--public meeting at Lytton Plaza, May 26 [1969], 905-64; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
    text on reverse about death of a demonstrator in Berkeley
  - A Young Man Is Deadd, 1969; 905-64; 11 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
    Political Activities- Rallies
  - A.S.S.U.- A.S.S.U. Election, 1969; 529-7; 11 x 17 inches (Box B3)
    Organizations, Student-General
  - Abortion: Morality and Legality, 1969; 359; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - ACT FOR OUR DEMANDS BOYCOTT, April 3rd Movement, 1969 May 12-13; 527-05; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
    Student demonstrations.
  - Africa Week 2007 "Building the Africa We Want" [schedule of events] Brought to you by the Stanford Afircan Students' Association with support from the Center for African Studies., 2010-005; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - African Culture, 1968; 19; 9x12 inches (Box A1)
    Art Exhibits
  - African Sculpture, 1966; 14; 22x14 (Box C1)
  - African sculpture from the Nooter Collection, 1968; 203-8; 10 x 13 inches (Box A1)
    Art and Architecture, Dept. of -- Museum events
  - Afro-American '68, 1968; 530-7; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Aims of the Nations in the World Conflict, 1941; 6; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
    Faculty/Staff -- Panel Discussions
  - Alfred Noyes in a lecture and reading "Poetry of Today.", 1897; 303; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - All Campus Rock and Roll Party, Un-dated; 5197; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
    Dances
  - All roads lead to the 1931 Big Game Gaieties, 509-4; 13 x 20 (Box B1)
    Big Game Gaieties
  - "All Tangled Up", 1905-; 513-58; 17 x 28 inches (Box C7)
  - "All Tangled Up", 1905-; 513-59; 17 x 28 inches (Box B3)
  - All those officially connected... to meet President and Mrs. Wilson, circa 1915; 4; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - All-Campus Dance, 1969; 5192; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
  - Alumni Directory, Un-dated; 702; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
    Alumni Activities
  - America's Hidden Arsenal: Chemical and Biological Warfare, 1968; 347; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - American Musicale, 1968; 524-26; 11 x 14 inches (Box not specified)
    Student Musical Groups
  - American Premiere. NIGHT FLIGHT by the distinguished Italian composer Luigi Dallapiccola in English and THERE AND BACK by Paul Hindemith in English. Professional soloists, Stanford Chorus, Stanford Symphony Orchestra. March [1962], 524-55; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Amnesty Meeting, Un-dated; 125; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - An Academic Profile of Jose Antonio Burciaga's Work. A Celebration of Jose Antonio's work and life. May 9, 1997, 212-3; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - An Easter Message, Un-dated; 385; 11 x 15 inches (Box A2)
  - An Evening of Playes by Shaw, Wilder, and Saroyan, Un-dated; 511-50; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - An Evening of Plays by 3 Stanford Playwrights, Un-dated; 513-56; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - An Evening with Bennet Cerf, 1962; 321; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - An Exhibition Featuring some Aspects of the Development of California Botany with emphasis on Central California and especially Jasper Ridge. Green Library 10 May through 15 August 1982. (hand-colored CA poppy drawing), 2007-016; 10.5 x 19.5 inches (Box C4)
    Mounted on board. From ASUL offices
    Libraries -- Exhibits
  - AN OPEN LETTER TO THE COMMUNITY. March 4, 1969. The Tresidder Union Board is sponsoring a pre-dead week FREE dance this Friday night, March 7, ...., 528-02; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box C4)
    Tresidder Memorial Union
  - Andrew Shanken UC Berkeley. 194X: American Architecture and ABstraction at Mid-Century. Architectural Theory and Practice Lecture. May 21, 2010- Cummings Art Building, 2010-016; 11 x 17.5 inches (Box B3)
  - Ansel Adams and Wallace Stegner: A Conversation, 1982 (Box B2)
  - Anti-Taxation Rally, Un-dated; 905-16; 11 x 14 inches (Box not specified)
  - "Antigone", 1902-; 513-5; 7 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Antiponh (Antigone). Stanford University April 17 and 19, 1902-., 513-3; 20 x 12 (Box C5)
    one copy in B1; there may be other copies in map case at SAL
    Drama Productions
  - April 22nd is national office staff day. May 7th is Stanford office staff day. Vote Yes! United Stanford Employees, Local 715. [no year noted], 2006-051; 19 x 14 inches (Box C4)
  - April 3rd. A Community Meeting on Stanford-SRI. Dinkelspiel--Thursday p 4:00 pm [1969. 3 paragraphs of text and list of organizations], 527-01; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box C4)
  - Are We Destroying the Bay, 1969; 361; 11 x 16 inches (Box A2)
  - Aris Fioretos April 2, 2009 [2 different talks, one on his book THE TRUTH ABOUT SASCHA KNISCH and one on Nelly Sachs], 2009-016; 11 x 14 inches (Box A3)
  - Aristophanes Clouds. An ancient satire with modern obscentieis...aimed at the academy. Friday & Saturday, 14-15 May 2010-. A SCIT production [Stanford Classics in Theater]., 2010-003; 17 x 22 inches (Box C10)
  - "Arms and the Man", 1933; 513-21; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - "Arms and the Man", Un-dated; 513-63; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Art Exhibits on Campus--Exhibition of Works by E.H. Blashfield, 1910; 902-9; 15x22 inches (Box C10)
  - Art Exhibits on Campus--Exhibitions of Etchings, 1909; 902-8; 11x16 inches (Box B3)
  - Art Exhibits on Campus--Joan Donegan--Paintings and Lithographs, Un-dated; 902-6; 11x17 inches (Box B3)
  - Art Exhibits on Campus--Oils by Giovannella, 1967; 902-5; 11x17 inches (Box B3)
  - Art Exhibits on Campus--Oils by Nancy O'Bannon, Un-dated; 902-3; 11x17 inches (Box B3)
  - Art Exhibits on Campus--Paintings and Sculpture by Jean McCandless, 1967; 902-4; 11x17 inches (Box B3)
  - Art Exhibits on Campus--Paintings by Nils Westerland, 1967; 902-1; 11x17 inches (Box B3)
  - Art Exhibits on Campus--Paintings by Ronald R. Kalla, 1967; 902-2; 11x17 inches (Box B3)
  - Art Exhibits on Campus--Studies in Direct Metal Sculpture by Hans Wehrli, 1967; 902-7 (Box B3)
  - Art Lecture, 1968; 348; 15 x 18 inches (Box C1)
  - "As You Like It", 1947; 511-10; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Ascent of the Matterhorn, 1900; 106; 9 x 12 inches (Box A1)
    Faculty/Staff -- Lectures
  - Ash Wednesday, 1968; 905-40; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
    Religious Services
  - Asian American Activities Center. Asian Images. Asian Heritage Week., 1983; 530-31; 23 x 17.5 inches (Box C9)
  - Asian American arts- Expressions of the Community, Un-dated (1970s?); 530-33; 17.5 x 22.5 inches (Box C9)
  - Asian Americans at Stanford, undated; 2009-266.2; 14 x 22 inches (Box C11)
  - Asian American Music: Joanne & Chris, undated; 2009-266.1; 17 x 22 inches (Box C11)
    Stanford University. Branner Hall
  - Asian American Studies Courses 1998-99, 2002-008; 11 x 17 inches (Box B1)
  - ASSU- "A Young Man's Fancy"- Spring Sing, Un-dated; 529-12; 22 x 28 inches (Box D2)
  - ASSU- "Big Game Week '68", 1968; 529-1; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - ASSU- "Good Grief: It's Spring!" Spring Sing, Un-dated; 529-11; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - ASSU- "Make Sure Your LASSU Rep. is Willing to Represent You!", 1968; 529-2; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - ASSU- "Vicki for ASSU Pres.", 1968; 529-3; 14 x 18 inches (Box B3)
  - ASSU- "Vote Yes for the New Constitution", 1968; 529-4; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - ASSU- A.S.S.U. Travel Service, 1969; 529-8; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - ASSU- Cory -Schulz Position Paper, 1969; 529-6; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - ASSU- Spiegel- Cornell Campaign Poster, 1969; 529-5; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - ASSU- Stu-Fac Winter Hostels, Un-dated; 529-10; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - ASSU- Student Body Assessment- One Dollar, Un-dated; 529-9; 7 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Astronomical Society of the Pacific, 1896; 905-27; 16 x 21 inches (Box not specified)
  - Athletics-Miscellaneous--Junior Day: Interclass Field Day, Varsity Independ'ts, 1904; 805-3; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
    Athletics -- Miscellaneous
  - Australia: An All Colored Motion Picture, 1961; 320; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Austria Today, 1968; 344; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Authors! Authors! Authors! Associates of the Stanford University Libraries & Stanford Bookstore Present Author Carnival 2004. Saturday April 17, 2004, 2006-038; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1911; 316; 11 x 14 inches (Box A6)
  - Baccalaureate Service, Un-dated; 28; 8x11 inches (Box A1)
    Religious Services-Baccalaureate
  - Baccalaureate Service, Un-dated; 28; 8 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - Bal-a-ka-boa, Un-dated; 905-19; 7 1/2 x 15 inches (Box not specified)
  - Band Dance, Un-dated; 5194; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baran and American Radicalism Today, 1966; 335; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
    Non-Stanford Speakers-Conferences
  - Barber Shop, Cigar Store--S.E. corner--Encina Hall basement, Un-dated; 30; 8 x 10 inches (Box B1)
  - Basball--California vs Stanford, Un-dated; 802-24; 13x21 inches (Box map case)
    Baseball
  - Baseball-- San Francisco vs Stanford, Un-dated; 802-40; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball-- San Jose Normal vs Stanford, Un-dated; 802-43; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball-- San Jose Professionals vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-31; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball-- San Jose vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-21; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball-- St. Mary's vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-63; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Alumni vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-50; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--California vs Stanford, Un-dated; 802-23; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--California vs Stanford, 1895; 802-1; 9 1/2x12 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--California vs Stanford, 1901-; 802-4; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--California vs Stanford, 1901-; 802-16; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--California vs Stanford, 1902-; 802-19; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--California vs Stanford, 1904; 802-9; 14x16 inches (Box map case)
  - Baseball--Clabrough Golcher, Un-dated; 802-66; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Fireman's Fund Ins. Co. vs Stanford Varsity, Un-dated; 802-56; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Fireman's Fund Ins. Co. vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-41; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Fireman's Fund vs Stanford, 1900; 802-2; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Firemen's Fund vs Stanford, 1900; 802-3; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Independent vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-20; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Interclass Basball, Un-dated; 802-11; 9 1/2x11 inches (Box A2)
  - Baseball--Interclass Basball Game, 1902-; 802-5; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Interclass Baseball Game, 1902-; 802-8; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Interclass Baseball Games, Un-dated; 802-26; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Portland Professionals vs Stanford, Un-dated; 802-58; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Portland vs Stanford, Un-dated; 802-62; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Presidio vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-33; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Presidio vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-37; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Santa Clara vs Stanford, Un-dated; 802-45; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Santa Clara vs Stanford, Un-dated; 802-51; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Santa Clara vs Stanford, Un-dated; 802-54; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Santa Clara vs Stanford, Un-dated; 802-61; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Santa Clara vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-29; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Santa Clara vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-53; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Santa Clara vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-64; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Santa Clara vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-65; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Sophomores vs Freshmen, Un-dated; 802-60; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Special Train Saturday, Un-dated; 802-6; 5x7 inches (Box map case)
  - Baseball--St. Mary's vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-22; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs Alumni, Un-dated; 802-13; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs Alumni, Un-dated; 802-44; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs Alumni, Un-dated; 802-47; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs California, Un-dated; 802-12; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs California, Un-dated; 802-14; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs California, 1900; 802-17; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs Fireman's Fund, Un-dated; 802-30; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs Firemen's Fund, 1902-; 802-7; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs Firemen's Fund, Un-dated; 802-28; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs Firemen's Fund, Un-dated; 802-42; 11x14 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs Firemen's Fund, Un-dated; 802-52; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs Olympics, Un-dated; 802-46; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs San Jose Professionals, Un-dated; 802-49; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs Santa Clara, Un-dated; 802-48; 91/2x12 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs Santa Clara, Un-dated; 802-55; 91/2x11 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs Santa Clara, Un-dated; 802-57; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Stanford vs Santa Clara, Un-dated; 802-32; 91/2x12 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Stanford will Play Santa Clara, Un-dated; 802-59; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Tufts-Lyons vs Stanford, Un-dated; 802-34; 91/2x12 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Varsity vs Alameda High School, Un-dated; 802-38; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Varsity vs Alumni, Un-dated; 802-27; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Varsity vs Olympics and Freshman vs. University of Pacific, Un-dated; 802-18; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Varsity vs Santa Clara, Un-dated; 802-10; i14x22n. (Box A4)
  - Baseball--Varsity vs Santa Clara, Un-dated; 802-15; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Varsity vs St. Mary's, Un-dated; 802-35; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Varsity vs The Elk Club of Oakland, Un-dated; 802-25; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Baseball--Varsity vs The Elks Club of Oakland, Un-dated; 802-36; 14x22 inches (Box map case)
  - Baseball First Intercollegiate Game California vs. Stanford at Stanford University Saturday April 5th, undated; 802-24; 13 x 21 inches (Box B1)
  - Baseball-Interclass Baseball, n.d; 802-11; 9.5x11 (Box map case)
  - Baseball-St. Mary's vs Varsity, Un-dated; 802-39; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Basketball Dance, Un-dated; 5195; 11 x 14 inches (Box C8)
  - Basketball (Men's)--2010-2011 Season, 2011-004; 14 x 22 inches (Box B2)
  - Basketball (Women's), 1995-1996; Accession ARCH-2016-133.03 (Box D2)
  - Basketball (Women's), 1989-1990; Accession ARCH-2016-133.02 (Box C8)
  - Basketball (Women's)--2010-2011 Season, 2011-005; 14 x 22 inches (Box B2)
  - Be Greet Players- "Twelfth Night", Un-dated; 903-7; 5 x 11 inches (Box A4)
    Dramatic Productions on Campus
  - Be in time! Be in time!, Un-dated; 530-14; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Before the Revolution, 1967; 203-4; 16 x 21 inches (Box C1)
  - "Belinda", 1921; 513-18; 11 x 14 inches (Box A3)
  - Ben Greet Players- "Much Ado About Nothing", Un-dated; 903-8; 14 x 22 inches (Box C10)
  - Ben Greet Players- "Much Ado About Nothing", Un-dated; 903-10; 14 x 22 inches (Box C10)
  - Ben Greet Players- "Much Ado About Nothing", Un-dated; 903-5; 11 x 16 inches (Box B3)
  - Bentley on Brecht, 1968; 342; 8.5 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Beta Theta Pi Nooner, 1969; 519-3; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
  - Big Game "C", Un-dated; 905-77; 12 x 20 inches (Box C9)
  - Big Game Gaieties, 1926; 509-1; 13 x 20 inches (Box C6)
  - Big Game Gaieties, 1929; 509-2; 13 x 20 inches (Box C6)
  - Big Game Gaieties, 1930; 509-3; 13 x 21 inches (Box C6)
  - Big Game Gaieties, 1931; 509-4; 13 x 20 inches (Box not specified)
  - Big Game Gaieties, 1932; 509-5; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Big Game Gaieties, 1933; 509-6; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Big Game Gaieties, 1952; 509-7; 15 x 20 inches (Box not specified)
  - Big Game Gaieties, 1952; 509-8; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Big Game Gaieties, 1961; 509-9; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Big Game Gaieties 1989 Don of the Dead. Presented by Ram's Head November 15, 16, 17., 2007-007; 16 x 21 inches (Box C4)
  - Big Game Gaieties 1998: Oceans Rise, Campuses Fall, Cal Sucks. Farmageddon., 509-11; 17x22.5 inches (Box not specified)
  - Big Game Gaieties 2001. Planet of the Weenies. Cal both sucks and blows. Ram's Head Theatrical Society., 2003-016; 15 x 23.5 inches (Box C4)
  - Big Game Gaieties: "Cardinal Sins", 1984; 509-12; 17 x 25 inches (Box D2)
  - "Big Game Gaities of 1952", 50810; 20 x 15 inches (Box A3)
    Ram's Head Productions
  - Big Game "S", Un-dated; 905-76; 12 x 20 in (Box C9)
  - Big Game Show - Tryouts, 1968; 5101; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box C6)
  - Big Game Week, 2004; 2015-025; 18 x 24 inches (Box C11)
  - "Billy Budd", 1952; 511-35; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - "Biography", 1951; 511-30; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - "Bird in Hand", Un-dated; 513-50; 14 x 19 inches (Box B3)
  - Bishop Edwin H. Hughes, Un-dated; 403; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Black Liberation Month Stanford University, 1998 Feb; 2002-005; 13 x 18.75 inches (Box B1)
  - Black Liberation Month/Centennial Celebration Stanford University February, 1991, 2004-002; 8.5 x 14 inches (Box A2)
    Lists events for Feb. 1-2, 1991
  - Black Student Union- "Black Girl in Search of God", 1968; 5202; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
    Organizations, Student-Political
  - Black Student Union- BSU- 3 Plays, 1969; 5201; 11 x 17 inches (Box A4)
  - BLACKFEST 2009, 39936; 2009-006; 17 x 11 inches (Box C6)
  - Bloch Symposium Friday and Saturday. Felix Bloch (1905-1983) / The Physics Department will celebrate.... [Centennial event]. Accompanied by program and Centennial folder., 1989 Oct 27-28; 2007-006; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Boycott Grapes, 1968; 905-55; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - BOYCOTT GRAPES / Stanford Grape Boycott Committee Announces its First Meeting Thurs. Oct. 3 [1968], 905-55; 9 x 12 inches (Box A3)
    hand-lettered sign
  - Bruce Connon 3 Films: a Movie Report Cosmic Ray, Un-dated; 203-12; 11 x 16 inches (Box A1)
  - Burciaga, Jose Antonio. "The Last Supper of Chicano Heroes" detail of mural... by Jose Antonio Burciaga, Stanford University., 1989; 130; 22 x 17 inches (Box C8)
    Faculty/Staff
  - Burciaga, Jose Antonio. Monumental bullring en Central America... (caricature of Kissinger as bull fighter), 1983; 131; 15 x 24 inches (Box D2)
  - "Burning Bright" by John Steinbeck, Un-dated; 513-73; 17 x 22.5 inches (Box C3)
  - "Burning Bright" by John Steinbeck, Un-dated; 513-73; 17x22.5 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
    [6/2007 need to verify that this item is truly in mc folder]
  - Business School Panel, Un-dated; 530-15; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
    Business, Graduate School of
  - C. R. Ashbee, Un-dated; 396; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - "Caesar and Cleopatra", Un-dated; 5074; 14 x 20 inches (Box C6)
  - California versus Stanford Berkeley Campus inter-collegiate baseball. Saturday, April 2, 1904, 2:30 p.m., 802-9; 14 x 16 inches (Box B1)
  - Campus Cyclery: Bicycles and Repairing, Un-dated; 530-25; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Campus Events Fall 1987. Produced Quarterly by the Tresidder Memorial Union., 2006-007; 17 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - Campus Events Spring 1988. Produced Quarterly by the Tresidder Memorial Union., 2006-006; 17 x 22 inches (Box C4)